https://eflowerwholesale.com/eflowerwholesale.com/privacy-policy/

Loading... Please wait...
Iris
Privacy NoticeThis privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for eflowerwholesale.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared. Eflowerwholesale.com do not share any of these information with any vendors. We only use information collected online for verifying with credit card institutions with the particular transaction.2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.Information Collection, Use, and Sharing We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. There will be times when we need to contact you or the recipient of the flowers when there are questions regarding the particular order.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:• See what data we have about you, if any.• Change/correct any data we have about you.• Have us delete any data we have about you.• Express any concern you have about our use of your data.Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the Web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 510-836-2200 or via email: OaklandFlowerMart@gmail.com.
Orders We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contactinformation (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.We use BigCommerce to process our orders online.
Here is BigCommerce privacy policy:Privacy Policy Per BigCommerceDate of Last Revision: September 10, 2019BigCommerce wants to help you better understand how we collect, use, protect, and share your personal data. This Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand your privacy choices when you visit our site, use our mobile app or any of our services. It does not apply to other websites or services that we do not control, including websites or services of other BigCommerce users.This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and forms an integral part of, the BigCommerce Terms of Service. The meaning of any capitalized term can be found in the Definitions section. Other terms may be defined in the Terms of Service. Please note that our services may vary by region. We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully and take the time to get to know our practices. If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please contact us at privacy@bigcommerce.com.1. Privacy Shield. BigCommerce complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States. BigCommerce has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles and will do so with respect to transfers of Personal Data from the United Kingdom to the United States. If there is any conflict between the terms in this Privacy Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit the U.S. Department of Commerce site at https://www.privacyshield.gov/BigCommerce is responsible for all onward transfers of Personal Data to third parties in accordance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework.2. Definitions.1. Information Types.a. “Account Information” means data about how and when a BigCommerce account is accessed and the features used.b. “Browser Information” means provided by a browser, including the IP address, the website visited, network connection, device information, and other data, including Cookies.c. “Contact Information” means basic personal details, including such information as first and last name, company name, email address, postal address, phone number, and may include social media account information.d. “Device Information” means information about your device, such as device ID number, model, and manufacturer, version of your operating system and geographical region, collected from any devices when accessing our website, using the Mobile App, or any of our Services.e. “Mobile App” means the BigCommerce Mobile Application available through third-party app stores for mobile devices.f. “Payment Information” means, for example, credit card, ACH or other payment information.g. “Security Information” means user ID, password and password hints, and other security information used for authentication and account access.h. “Support Information” includes hardware, software, authentication data, chat session contents, error reports, performance data, and other communication or technical information and may, with express permission, include remote access to facilitate troubleshooting.i. “Usage Information" means information collected when you interact with the BigCommerce website, mobile application or any of our services, including functionalities accessed, pages visited, and other interaction data.j. “Transaction Information” means the data related to transactions that occur on our platform, including product, order, shipping information, Contact Information, and Payment Information.2. “Automated Decision Making” means a decision made solely by automated means without human involvement.3. “Controller” means an entity that determines the purposes and means of the Processing of Personal Data.4. “Cookie” a small file that resides on your computer’s hard drive that often contains an anonymous unique identifier that is accessible by the website that placed it there, but is not accessible by other sites.5. “Merchant” means an entity that has used or is using Services the for ecommerce.6. “Partner” means a separate legal entity that is a participant in our Agency Partner Program, our Technology Partner Program or other third-party technology integration with the BigCommerce platform, a theme designer, reseller, or referrer of the Services.7. “Personal Data” means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person identifiable information under applicable data protection laws and regulations.8. “Processing” means any operation or set of operations which is performed upon Personal Data, whether or not by automatic means, including, but not limited to, alteration, collection, organization, recording, retrieval, storage, transmission, and use.9. “Processor” means the entity which processes Personal Data on behalf of the Controller10. “Sensitive Personal Data” means any data that reveals racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership, genetic data, biometric data for the purpose of uniquely identifying a natural person, or data concerning health or a natural person’s sex life and/or sexual orientation.11. “Shopper” means an entity that interacts with the ecommerce offering of a Merchant through the BigCommerce platform.3. Merchants.1. Merchant Policies. Merchants should help Shoppers understand how the Merchant, BigCommerce and relevant third parties collect and process Shoppers’ Personal Data. To that end, Merchants must:. post an accurate privacy policy on their storefront that complies with all applicable laws and regulations;a. process Personal Data in accordance with applicable laws and, to the extent required under such laws, provide notice to and obtain informed consent from Shoppers for the use and access of their Personal Data by BigCommerce and other third parties; andb. if the Merchant is collecting any Sensitive Personal Data from Shoppers, obtain affirmative, explicit, and informed consent andallow such Shoppers to revoke their consent to the use and access of Sensitive Personal Data at any time.2. Information Collected.. When a Merchant interacts with our Website, for example, by signing up for a trial, a subscription, or a newsletter, or performing transactions, BigCommerce may collect and control information such as Account Information, Browser Information, Contact Information, Payment Information, Support Information, Device Information, Security Information, Usage Information and set a Cookie.a. When a Merchant interacts with our Mobile App, BigCommerce may collect and control information such as Account Information, Contact Information, Device Information, Usage Information and Security Information.3. Information Usage. We use this information to provide Merchants with our Services, confirm identities, provide support such as debugging, troubleshooting, automated decision making such as the detection of fraudulent account creation when signing up for our service, for advertising and marketing, invoicing, to resolve incidents related to the use of our Website and Services, to improve and personalize our Services, such as push notifications regarding your store activities, and to comply with legal requirements. We may use this information in other cases where we have received express permission.4. Partners.1. Information Collected. When a Partner signs up for a partner account or signs up a Merchant for our Services, BigCommerce may collect and control information such as Account Information, Browser Information, Contact Information, Payment Information, Support Information, Security Information, and Usage Information.2. Information Usage. We use this information to provide Partners with our Services, confirm identities, provide support, for advertising and marketing, invoicing, to resolve incidents related to the use of our Website and Services, to improve and personalize our Services, and to comply with legal requirements. We may use this information in other cases where we have received express permission.5. Shoppers.1. Information Collected. When Shoppers interact with a Merchant’s ecommerce offering through the BigCommerce platform, we may collect and process Browser Information and Transaction Information of the Shopper on behalf of the Merchant.2. Information Usage. We use this information as a Processor to provide our Services to Merchants, support and process orders, improve and personalize our Services, and manage risk and fraud.6. Visitors.1. Information Collected. When visitors browse our Website, or engage in communications with us online or offline, we may collect and control, as applicable, Browser Information, Support Information, Contact Information, and Usage Information submitted or communicated to us.2. Information Usage. We use this information to provide our Services, and improve and personalize communications, interactions, our Services, and provide support if needed.7. Communications.1. Promotional. We may deliver and personalize our communications with Merchants, Partners, and visitors. For example, we may notify a Merchant by email or other means when a subscription is ending, or invite the recipient to participate in a survey. For information about managing email subscriptions and promotional communications, please go to our email preferences page.2. Account. We send certain required communications, such as account notices or information, to users of our Services. You may not opt out of receiving these communications if you have an active storefront.8. Information Sharing. Our Services are possible because of a variety of third parties and service providers. Sometimes it is necessary to share Merchant, Partner, or Shopper Personal Data with them to support our Services. We may access, transfer, disclose, and/or preserve that Personal Data with consent or in the following circumstances.1. Compliance. If we have a good faith belief that doing so is necessary to: (i) comply with applicable law or respond to valid legal process, including from law enforcement or other government agencies;or (ii) protect the rights or property of BigCommerce, including enforcing the terms governing the use of the Services.2. Protection. If we have a good faith belief that doing so is necessary to: (i) protect Merchants, Partners, Shoppers, or visitors; for example, to prevent spam or attempts to defraud us or users of our Services, or in response to threats of safety of any person; (ii) operate and maintain the security of our products, including to prevent or stop an attack on our computer systems or networks.3. Affiliates. We share Personal Data among BigCommerce-controlled affiliates and subsidiaries.4. Service Providers. BigCommerce may use from time to time a limited number of third-party service providers, data processors, contractors, and other businesses to assist us in providing our Services for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.5. SDKs and APIs. BigCommerce may include third-party libraries such as Software Development Kits (SDKs) or Application Interfaces (APIs) within our applications (including the Mobile App) for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, including the following:0. Functional SDKs: these are software libraries we use to enhance the end user experience and functionality within the application, such as graphics and display of images within the app, and in-app notifications according to preferences.1. Analytics SDKs: these are external third-party sub processors’ libraries we use in collecting device and usage data for application performance monitoring.6. Payment Processing. We share payment data with banks and other entities that process payment transactions or provide other financial services, and for fraud prevention and credit risk reduction.7. Apps. Upon receiving a Merchant’s consent to install an application, we will share the Merchant’s Contact Information and other information requested by the app with the app Partner.8. Merger; Sale. We may also disclose Personal Data as part of a corporate transaction such as a merger or sale of assets.9. Automated Decision-Making. Some Personal Data may be used in Automated Decision Making to help us screen accounts for risk, fraud, or abuse concerns. You can contest or dispute such decision by reaching out to our 24/7 customer support team.10. Cookies. Cookies can be used to recognize you when you visit our Website, remember your preferences, and give you a personalized experience. Third party integrations on our Website also use Cookies. By using our Website or Services, you are agreeing to the use of Cookies and similar technologies for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. It possible to disable Cookies through your device or browser settings, but doing so may affect your ability to use the Website. The method for disabling Cookies may vary by device and browser, but can usually be found in preferences or security settings. To find out more about Cookies, including how to see what Cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit allaboutcookies.org, or aboutcookies.org. Because there is no consistent industry understanding of how to respond to “Do Not Track” signals, we do not alter our data collection and usage practices when we detect such a signal from your browser.11. AdRoll. BigCommerce works with AdRoll retargeting, which uses technology including web beacons and Cookies to collect data about our website usage and to improve the effectiveness of our marketing. Data recorded through the use of this technology is aggregated and shared with us. For more information or to opt-out of AdRoll and their partners, please visit this link.12. Third Party Application Stores: Third party application stores, such as Apple’s App Store or Google’s Google Play, might collect additional information and share them with us. Please refer to the application store’s Privacy Policy to better understand how they process any of the personal information they collect and share with app publishers like ourselves.13. Information Protection.1. We maintain administrative, technical, and physical security measures designed to provide reasonable protection for Personal Data against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, loss, and misuse. These security measures include access controls, encryption, and firewalls. We are certified as a PCI DSS Level 1 compliant service provider, which is the highest level of compliance available, and our platform is audited annually by independent third-party qualified security assessors against the ISO 27001 security standard. Unfortunately, no method of Internet use, datatransmission, or electronic storage is completely secure, so we cannot guarantee the absolute security of Personal Data.2. While we are dedicated to securing our Website and Services, you are responsible for securing and maintaining the privacy of your passwords and account information. We are not responsible for protecting Personal Data shared with a third-party based on an account connection that you have authorized.14. Accountability for Onward Transfer.1. Privacy Shield. We provide services around the world. To provide our Services, it may be necessary to transmit Personal Data outside of the country, state, or province where the data was received. As a participant in the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework, we are subject to the regulatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.2. Data Processors. We will only share or disclose Personal Data to the Processors identified here, which are contractually obligated to provide at least the same level of privacy protection required by the principles underlying the Privacy Shield. Furthermore, we will obligate any Processor to the specified, explicit and legitimate purposes consistent with your consent.3. Remedial Measures. If we learn Personal Data is not protected according to our contract, or is being processed beyond your consent, we will take reasonable steps to protect your information and/or cease its illegitimate processing.15. Access to Your Personal Data.1. We understand that you have rights over your Personal Data, and provide reasonable steps to allow you to access, correct, amend, delete, port, or limit the use of your Personal Data. This includes the right to withdraw, at any time, your consent for our collection and use. Additionally, you may have the right to make a complaint with the Data Protection Authority in your country.2. Merchants, Shoppers, and Partners are able to update many types of collected Personal Data directly within their accounts. Please contact us if you are unable to access or otherwise change your Personal Data within your account, or if you are concerned about other data collected.3. Shoppers, we are a Processor to your Merchant. You may also wish to contact your Merchant(s) directly regarding your Personal Data they havecollected. We can only forward your request to them. Any deletion or limitation on the use of your Personal Data may negatively affect your use of our Services.16. Enforcement; Recourse. In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, BigCommerce commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact BigCommerce at: privacy@bigcommerce.com orBigCommerce, Inc.11305 Four Points Austin, TX 78726 Attention: General CounselBigCommerce will respond to any such inquiries or complaints within forty-five (45) days. If BigCommerce fails to respond or its response is insufficient or does not address the concern, BigCommerce has registered with the Association of National Advertisers (ANA) to provide independent third party dispute resolution at no cost to the complaining party. To contact ANA and/or learn more about the company’s dispute resolution services, including instructions for submitting a complaint, please visit https://thedma.org/resources/consumer-resources/privacyshield-consumers/. Complaining parties may also, in absence of a resolution by BigCommerce and ANA, seek to engage in binding arbitration through the Privacy Shield Panel.ANA Contact Information:ANA Attn: Privacy Shield 225 Reinekers Lane, Suite 325 Alexandria, Virginia 22314BigCommerce also commits to periodically reviewing and verifying the accuracy of this Privacy Policy and the company’s compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, and remedying issues identified. All employees of BigCommerce that have access to Personal Data covered by this Privacy Policy are responsible for conducting themselves in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Failure of a BigCommerce employee to comply with this Privacy Policy may result in disciplinary action. BigCommerce is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC).Cookies We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.
Categories
Cut Flowers Misc
Leis
Orchids
Plants
Succulents
Carnations
Alstroemeria
All prices are in USD. © 2020 E Flower Wholesale.
Sitemap |
Shopping Cart Software by BigCommerce | Shipping Information
